chatporno.com 2019-01-23

# www.chatporno.com - Privacy policy

25 May 2018

Data protection is of a particularly high priority for our company. During the processing we conform to the requirements of the applicable data protection legislation, notably the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). This means we:

  * **clearly specify our purposes** before we process personal data, by using this Privacy Statement;
  * **limit our collection of personal data** to only the personal data needed for legitimate purposes;
  * first **ask for explicit permission** to process your personal data in cases where your permission is required;
  * take **appropriate security measures** to protect your personal data and we demand the same from parties who process personal data on our behalf;
  * **respect** your right to inspect, correct or delete your personal data held by us.

is the party responsible for all data processing. In this privacy statement, we will explain which personal data we collect and for which purposes. We recommend that you read it carefully.

## Registration

Certain features of our service require you to register beforehand. You will have to provide some information about yourself and choose a username and password for the account that we will set up for you.  
For this purpose, we use your name and address details, phone number, invoice address, email address, payment details and nickname.We need this data because of our agreement with you. We store this information until you close your account.  
We will retain this data so that you do not have to re-enter it every time you visit our website, and in order to contact you in connection with the execution of the agreement and to provide an overview of the services you bought on the platform. 

## Ewallet load

Via www.chatporno.com you can load credit in your Ewallet to buy services from other parties. This requires certain personal information. We share this with the payment providers to facilitate Ewallet loads.

For this purpose, we use your name and address details, invoice address, email address and payment details. We need this data because of our agreement with you. We store this information during the legal retention period imposed by the tax regulator.

## Promotion

We can inform you about new products or services through our newsletter. You can object at all times against this promotional communication. Every e-mail contains a cancellation link. 

The consent to the data storage of personal data, which you have given for the newsletter, may be revoked at any time. For the purpose of revocation of consent, a corresponding link is found in each newsletter. It is also possible to unsubscribe from the newsletter any time directly on the platform.

## Advertisements

Our website shows generic advertisements. We do not collect personal data for this purpose.

## Cookies

The website uses cookies. Cookies are text files that are stored in a computer system via an Internet browser. We do this to improve the functioning of our website and to recognize you during multiple visits. This way, you do not have to log in every time and we remember important settings and preferences. We do not share cookie data with third parties and do not target advertisements based on cookies.

You can disable cookies through your browser settings but this may render some functionality unusable.

## Providing Data to Third Parties

Except for the parties mentioned above, we do not under any circumstance provide your personal data to other companies or organisations, unless we are required so by law.

## Statistics

We keep statistics on the use of the website, giving us access to individual data. We use these statistics to improve presentation and functioning of the website. However, we only access individual data insofar as necessary for the purposes set out in this statement.

## Security

We take appropriate security measures to reduce misuse of and unauthorised access to personal data.

## Changes to this Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to modify this statement. We recommend that you consult this statement on a regular basis, so that you remain informed of any changes.

## Inspection and Modification of your Data

You can always contact us if you have any questions regarding our privacy policy or wish to review, modify or delete your personal data.

You have the following right:

  * Being informed on which personal data we have and what we are using it for;
  * Inspection of the personal data that we keep from you;
  * Having incorrect data corrected;
  * Request to delete outdated personal data;
  * Revoke your consent;
  * Object to certain uses.

Please note that you always make clear who you are, so that we can assure that we do not modify or remove the data from the wrong person.

## Complaints

If you think that we are not helping you in the right way, you have the right to lodge a complaint at the data protection authority in your country if you are based in the European Union. For example in the The Netherlands, the Autoriteit Persoonsgegevens.

## Contact details

Phone:   
Email:   
Website: www.chatporno.com
